{
   "allUser": 15,
   "respondedUser": 2,
   "sendResponse": [
       {
           "name": "Motam Shiva Teja",
           "questionAnswers": [
               {
                   "question": "What is your name?",
                   "answer": "Motam Shiva Teja"
               },
               {
                   "question": "What is your Supervisor's Name?",
                   "answer": "Dhanush"
               },
               {
                   "question": "Do you prefer working at the office instead??",
                   "answer": "Slightly"
               },
               {
                   "question": "Do you recommend remote working to your friends?",
                   "answer": "Not at all"
               },
               {
                   "question": "Do you think remote working has affected you positively?",
                   "answer": "Moderately"
               },
               {
                   "question": "How long do you work remotely?",
                   "answer": "Extremely"
               }
           ]
       },
       {
           "name": "Lavesh Goyal",
           "questionAnswers": [
               {
                   "question": "What is your name?",
                   "answer": "Lavesh Goyal"
               },
               {
                   "question": "What is your Supervisor's Name?",
                   "answer": "Dhanush"
               },
               {
                   "question": "Do you prefer working at the office instead??",
                   "answer": "Slightly"
               },
               {
                   "question": "Do you recommend remote working to your friends?",
                   "answer": "Not at all"
               },
               {
                   "question": "Do you think remote working has affected you positively?",
                   "answer": "Moderately"
               },
               {
                   "question": "How long do you work remotely?",
                   "answer": "Extremely"
               }
           ]
       }
   ]
}
